[
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these blocks in &quot;Minecraft&quot; has the lowest blast resistance?",
    "correct_answer": "Sand",
    "incorrect_answers": ["End Stone", "Water", "Wood Planks"]
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which of the following physicists did NOT work on the Manhattan project?",
    "correct_answer": "Murray Gell-Mann",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Richard Feynman",
      "J. Robert Oppenheimer",
      "John Von-Neumann"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
    "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?",
    "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Beyond Good and Evil", "The Republic", "Meditations"]
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "question": "In the film &quot;Requiem for a Dream&quot;, what drug does Jared Leto&#039;s character get addicted to?",
    "correct_answer": "Heroin",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Cocaine", "Marijuana", "Oxycodone"]
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
    "question": "Which cartoon family lives in 31 Spooner Street, Quahog, Rhode Island USA?",
    "correct_answer": "The Griffins",
    "incorrect_answers": ["The Simpsons", "The Jetsons", "The Hills"]
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
    "question": "How many plays is Shakespeare generally considered to have written?",
    "correct_answer": "37",
    "incorrect_answers": ["18", "54", "25"]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Science: Gadgets",
    "question": "Microphones can be used not only to pick up sound, but also to project sound similar to a speaker.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Hundred Years&#039; War was fought for more than a hundred years.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
  }
]
